{
	"DbmsQuestions" : {
		"1" : {
			"question" : "A logical schema",
			"option1" : "Is the entire database",
			"option2" : "describe data in terms of relational tables",
			"option3" : "Describes how data is actually stored on disk",
			"option4" : "Both (A) and (C)",
			"answer" : "Is the entire database"
		},
		"2" : {
			"question" : "The way a particular application views the data from the database that the application uses is a",
			"option1" : "Module",
			"option2" : "Relational model",
			"option3" : "Schema",
			"option4" : "Sub schema",
			"answer" : "Sub schema"
		},
		"3" : {
			"question" : "A relational database developer refers to a record as",
			"option1" : "A criteria",
			"option2" : "A relation",
			"option3" : "A tuple",
			"option4" : "An attribute",
			"answer" : "A tuple"
		},
		"4" : {
			"question" : "Database is generally __________",
			"option1" : "System-centered",
			"option2" : "User-centered",
			"option3" : "Company-centered",
			"option4" : "Data-centered",
			"answer" : "User-centered"
		},
		"5" : {
			"question" : "A characteristic of an entity",
			"option1" : "Relation",
			"option2" : "Parameter",
			"option3" : "Attribute",
			"option4" : "Constraint",
			"answer" : "Attribute"
		},
		"6" : {
			"question" : "Object=_________+relationships",
			"option1" : "data",
			"option2" : "attributes",
			"option3" : "entity",
			"option4" : "constraints",
			"answer" : "entity"
		},
		"7" : {
			"question" : "DBMS manages the interaction between __________ and database.",
			"option1" : "End Users",
			"option2" : "Users",
			"option3" : "Clients",
			"option4" : "Stake Holders",
			"answer" : "End Users"
		},
		"8" : {
			"question" : "IMS stands for?",
			"option1" : "Information Mastering System",
			"option2" : "Instruction Management System",
			"option3" : "Instruction Manipulating System",
			"option4" : "Information Management System",
			"answer" : "Information Management System"
		},
		"9" : {
			"question" : "E-R model uses this symbol to represent weak entity set?",
			"option1" : "Dotted rectangle",
			"option2" : "Diamond",
			"option3" : "Doubly outlined rectangle",
			"option4" : "None of these",
			"answer" : "Doubly outlined rectangle"
		},
		"10" : {
			"question" : "Key to represent relationship between tables is called",
			"option1" : "Primary key",
			"option2" : "Secondary Key",
			"option3" : "Foreign Key",
			"option4" : "None of these",
			"answer" : "Foreign Key"
		}
	}
}